Finding aid to the Mary Daly papers SSC.MS.00637
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES I. Professional, 1954-2011; 15.418 linear feet (19 containers)
  - Letters of Support / Original Copies, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Misc. Professional Materials, 1987-1999 (Box 10)
  - BC Heights and Others Articles on THE EVENT and Harassment (Box 10)
  - Speaking Engagements, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Misc. Professional Materials, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Speaking, 2004-2005 (Box 10)
  - BC Stationary (Box 10)
  - Flyers - Undine Pawlowski, 2004-2006 (Box 10)
  - Support Letters, 1991-1999 (Box 10)
  - Notes (Box 10)
  - Intro to Feminist Ethics, 1977-1979 (Box 10)
  - Speaking Engagements, 2003-2004 (Box 11)
  - Denison University - Ohio, 2003-2004 (Box 11)
  - BC Courses, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Mythic Patterns / Spring, 1979 (Box 11)
  - BC Course Materials / Spring, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Phil. Critiques / Fall, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Feminist Ethics II (Th. 556) / Spring, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Phil. (Th. 558) / Spring, 1984 (Box 11)
  - BC Mythic Patterns / Fall, 1984 (Box 11)
  - BC Phil/ (Th. 557) / Fall, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Intro to Feminist Ethics (Th. 251), 1984 (Box 11)
  - Feminist Ethics / Fall, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Mythic Patterns II / Spring, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Intro to Feminist Ethics (Th. 251) / Spring, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Phil. Texts (Th. 558) / Spring, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Harassment, 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Letters of Recommendation for Full Professorship, 1989 (Box 11)
  - BC Fight - Letters to-from Barth and Noonan, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - BC Fight - Copies of Letters to Supporters, 1989 (Box 11)
  - BC Fight - Vatican/Radical Feminism, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Full Professorship Rejection Letter, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Letters of Protest and Support, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Letters of Recommendation to Full Professorship, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Mary Daly Defense Fund, 1989 (Box 11)
  - BC Courses - The Women's Revolution and Theological Development / Fall, 1971 (Box 11)
  - BC Courses - Women's Liberation and the Church / Spring, 1972 (Box 11)
  - BC Courses, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Feminist Ethics / Fall, 1979 (Box 11)
  - BC Material / Spring, 1980 (Box 11)
  - BC Pile on Floor / Fall, 1983 (Box 11)
  - BC Syllabi / Fall, 1984 (Box 11)
  - BC / Spring, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Intro to Feminist Ethics (Th. 302) / Fall, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Feminist Ethics (Th. 554) / Spring, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Mythic Patterns (Th. 564) / Spring, 1979 (Box 11)
  - BC Course Evaluations / Fall, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Feminist Ethics / Spring, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Feminist Ethics I / Fall, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Intro Feminist Ethics - Course Critiques / Fall, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Intro to FE, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Intro to Feminist Ethics, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Dossier Vol. I (Box 12)
  - Phil Texts / Spring, 1980 (Box 12)
  - BTI Course Descriptions, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Feminist Philosophy (Th. 557) Course Critiques / Fall, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Petition in Support of Full Professorship, 1988 (Box 12)
  - BC Book Orders / Fall, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Salary, Yearly Increments and Some Sample Yearly Reports, 1982-1989 (Box 12)
  - TIAA CREF, 1998-1999 (Box 12)
  - BC Benefits, 1972-1995 (Box 12)
  - TIAA CREF, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Course Materials [?] (Box 12)
  - My Website, 2001-2006 (Box 12)
  - Undino - Speaking Engagements, 2004-2006 (Box 12)
  - Notes (Box 12)
  - BC Fight, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Media Info, 2000-2006 (Box 12)
  - BC Courses / Spring, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Ireland, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Ireland Speech, 1987 (Box 12)
  - BC Women's Studies / Fall, 1998 (Box 12)
  - Italy (Speaking), 2002-2006 (Box 12)
  - Letters of Support Against Firing, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Lakeside News, 2003-2006 (Box 12)
  - NOW Newsletter, 2003 (Box 12)
  - World Can't Wait, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Germany, Gudrun Nositschka, 2008 (Box 12)
  - Speaking Invitations, 2008 (Box 12)
  - Helen Caddes - Speaking Inquiry, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Speaking Enagements, 2004-2005 (Box 12)
  - MD Defense Fund List of Donors, 1999-2000 (Box 12)
  - Most Important Donors - MDDF (Box 12)
  - Duplicate Billing Records, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Gretchen - BC, Emily Mann's Draft, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Van Ness, Gretchen - Settlement Papers, 2000 (Box 12)
  - BC Case - Deposition of Joseph M. Herlihy, 2000 (Box 12)
  - BC Case - Deposition of Donald Dietrich, 2000 (Box 12)
  - BC Case - Deposition of Leo Sullivan, 2000 (Box 13)
  - BC Case - Deposition of Paul Breines, 2000 (Box 13)
  - BC Trial Info, Deposition of Richard Huber, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Van Ness (BC Case), 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - Sossman, Martha on Preliminary Injunction, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Defense Fund - Global Congress, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - McQuay (BC Case), 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - BC Case Articles, 1999 (Box 13)
  - MD Defense Fund, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Brain Trust List for "Dispelling the Demons (Box 13)
  - Defense Fund - Dagmar Kohring, 1999 (Box 13)
  - BC Case Articles, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - Defense Fund - Posters (Box 13)
  - BC Case Press Coverage, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Religious Studies News Interview, 1999 (Box 13)
  - BC Case Press, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 13)
  - BC Case Globe Coverage, 1999 (Box 13)
  - BC Case Petitions and Support (Box 13)
  - BC Case Press - Bronski, Michael, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Newspapers and Journals, 1997-2000 (Box 13)
  - "What is Enlightenment?" Interview, 1999 (Box 13)
  - BC Fact Book, 1978 (Box 13)
  - BC Course Critiques, 1970 (Box 13)
  - BC Faculty, 1965-1981 (Box 13)
  - Boston Theological Institute, 1969-1972 (Box 13)
  - BC Catalogs, 1997-1999 (Box 13)
  - University of Oregon, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Potential Book Reviews, Comments on New Website, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Presentation Poster (Box 13)
  - The Roseanne Show (Box 13)
  - Notes (Box 13)
  - AAR Gray, Edward (Interview), 1999 (Box 13)
  - Ralph Nader, 2000 (Box 13)
  - BC Propaganda (Box 13)
  - BC Case - BC Magazine Article, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Palumbo, Cathleen (aka Maude) - Financial Calculations, 1994 (Box 13)
  - BC Fight, 1982-1999 (Box 13)
  - Letters of Support BC, 1999 (Box 13)
  - The Observer, 1999 (Box 13)
  - AAR Membership, 1997-2000 (Box 13)
  - AAUP Letter, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Hood College Speaking Engagement, 2007 (Box 13)
  - Duplicate of Most of Materials Given to Lawyers, 1999 (Box 13)
  - PRA CIR, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - "Collection" for BC Case, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Ellen Goodman Letter, 1999 (Box 13)
  - McQuay To Counsel, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Wilt, Judith Deposition, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Gretchen -- Plaintiff, 2001 (Box 13)
  - BC Case Media, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Monan, J. Donald and Neenan, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Trial, Notice to Appear, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Daly vs. BC, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Gretchen Van Ness, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - Gretchen -- Notice to McQuay of Intent to Depose Leahy and Burgess, 2000 (Box 13)
  - NWSA -- Academic Discrimination Task Force, 2000 (Box 13)
  - BC Defendants' Notes, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Van Ness to Herlihy, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Motion for Preliminary Injunction, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - Gretchen -- Motion to Counsel, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Press Contacts, 1999 (Box 13)
  - University Statutes, 1999 (Box 14)
  - NWSA Newsletter on Daly's Case, 2001 (Box 14)
  - Gail Bryan, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Daly Protests -- Rice at Boston College, 2006 (Box 14)
  - Roseanne Barr Receipt, 2007 (Box 14)
  - American Academy of Religion, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Audre Lorde Open Letter (Box 14)
  - Pellegrini Raho, 2006 (Box 14)
  - Clippings -- Some Lectures, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - Nobel Conference, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Publicity Boston Conference Underground Church, 1968 (Box 14)
  - Clippings, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Letters of Support, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Harvard Walkout, 1971-1982 (Box 14)
  - Publicity Flyers, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
  - Emails from Mary Daly Website, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Whittier College, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Burning Times, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Info Packets for Press/Media and/or "Serious" Activists, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Misc. Notes (Box 14)
  - Religious Pamphlet and Calendar Including Daly, 1995 (Box 14)
  - Professional Engagements and Correspondence, Political Articles, 1990-2006 (Box 14)
  - Women's Spirituality Series, 2005 (Box 14)
  - HDS Conference Religion and the Feminist Movement, 2002 (Box 14)
  - Notes and Misc Papers, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Curriculum and 1970s, 1987-1989 (Box 14)
  - Attorneys Gertner, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Attorneys Alette Reed, 1975-1980 (Box 14)
  - Th 55301 Feminist Studies I BC Course Critiques, 1974 (Box 14)
  - BC Course Critiques, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Course Evaluations: Myth Patterns/Patriarchy II, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Th 5540189S Feminist Ethics, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Daly's Notes from Sessions with Gladys Custance, Spiritualist Adviser and Leader on Onset Spiritualist Church Community, 1970-1990 (Box 14)
  - Gary MacEoin "The World that Made Me, The World I Made" Draft, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Paper Written for a Daly Class by Jane Caputi, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Daly Profile, Sojourner, 1978 (Box 14)
  - BC Course Critiques Feminist Ethics I, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Mary Daly Dossier Vol. I, 1988 (Box 14)
  - BC Courses, 1988-1990 (Box 14)
  - Application for Promotion to Full Professorship, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Mary Daly Dossier Vol. 2, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Feminist Ethics Evaluations (Box 14)
  - Gyn/Ecology Reviews, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
  - Pure Lust, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Course Evaluations (Box 14)
  - Speaking Engagements, Misc., 2004-2007 (Box 14)
  - Misc. Leaflets, Notes about Feminist and Eco. Activities (Box 14)
  - Hye Sook Hwang, 2005-2007 (Box 15)
  - Women Ripped Off by Husbands, etc. (Box 15)
  - Intros to Male Book, 1969-1973 (Box 15)
  - Useful Articles for Research (Box 15)
  - Notes (Box 15)
  - American Academy of Religion Panel, 2010-2011 (Box 15)
  - Roseanne Barr (Box 15)
  - Misc. Notes (Box 15)
  - Misc. (Box 15)
  - BC Firing Media / BC History / MDDF, 1999-2006 (Box 15)
  - Elemental Feminist Philosophy, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Misc. Notes (Box 15)
  - Speaking Engagements, Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Tallahassee, Florida (Speaking), 2003 (Box 15)
  - Housatonic College, Blooroot (Speaking), 2001-2003 (Box 15)
  - Speaking - Cambridge, MA (Harvard), 2001 (Box 15)
  - Cairo (Speaking), 2001 (Box 15)
  - Newham College, Copyright Permissions, 2002 (Box 15)
  - Ball State U., Indiana (Speaking), 2003 (Box 15)
  - Notes found in The Basic Works of Aristotle (Box 15)
  - Notes found in On Photography (Box 15)
  - Notes found in Creativity and The Making of a Counter Culture (Box 15)
  - Notes found in Ancient Egyptian Religion (Box 15)
  - Notes found in Report from Iron Mountain (Box 15)
  - Notes found in One-Dimensional Man (Box 15)
  - List of male students in Daly's classes (Box 15)
  - Janice Raymond dissertation (Box 15)
  - Mary Daly Defense Fund and Other Miscellaneous T-Shirts (Box 67)
  - Wand (Box 67)
  - "I'm A Revolting Hag" Pin (Box 67)
  - Mary Daly Defense Fund Bumper Stickers (Box 67)
  - The Heights Newspapers, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - Poster for Quintessence Appearance at Vanderbilt University, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Video recording of Mary Daly on Channels 5 and 2, 1999-08-10; 1 items (1 VHS video cassette) (Box 74)
  - Video recording of The Roseanne Show with Mary Daly, 1999-04-13; 3 items (2 VHS videocassettes and 1 S-VHS videocassette) (Box 74)
  - Video recording of The Today Show - Gretchen van Ness with Mary Daly, 1999-08-18; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Video recording of WGBH Greater Boston featuring Amazon Grace, 2006-02-13; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette ) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of "Feminist Ethics" and "SULA" by Toni Morrison, 1979-11-20; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - "Feminist Ethics, 1999-10-02; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - "Feminist Ethics, 1979-02-13; 4 items (4 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly and Boston College - GBH Journal, Aimee Sands, 1979-02-16; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of MLA - Chicago - Stanley, Daly, Lorde, 1977; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - philosophy, Aristotle, friendship, 1979-11-05; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - KPBS segment, 1985-12-10; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - part of speech in Sheffield, 1988-04-25; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - Feminist Philosopher, Re-Calling the Courage to Sail: on Being a Radical Feminist Pirate in the 1990's - Colby College, 1991-02-28; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - Second Opinion with Erwin Knoll, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - Australian Broadcasting Corporation - Coming Out Show, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly interview with Joan Marles, San Francisco, 1992-11-24; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly interview (with Wittig, Rochefort, Servan-Schreiber), 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly in Berk., 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly on radical feminism - 90.9 WBUR, Connection, 2000-11-02; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly at UCLA (Pacifica Radio), 1987-11-25; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - "The Fire of Female Fury" (Pacifica Radio), 1980; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - "Wicked Words for Wild Women" (Pacifica Radio), 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly at Norwalk Community College, 1992-04-13; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly at Linfield College, 1982-05-06; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Jennifer Abod, 2 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Jennifer Abod - WXPN - Feminist Talk, 1980-1981; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture (The Women's Center), 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture, 1978; 1 items (1 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture - defective tape, 1 items (1 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture, 1977; 1 items (1 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture - Liberty Hall, 1 items (1 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly being interviewed by astrologer - Lomsey Poole, Rockport, MA, 1978; 1 items (1 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture to a French organization, 1982-04-14; 1 items (1 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture - Dublin, 1 items (1 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly lecture, 1979-02-12; 1 items (1 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Mary Daly - "Wicked Wprds for Wild Women" - UCLA, 1987-11-25; 1 items (1 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - W.I.T.C.H. Feminist Lecture Series Flyer, 1987 (Box 73)
  - Poster for Daly Reading at University of Frankfurt, 1986 (Box 73)
  - women@work Women's History Month California State University Poster, 2000 (Box 73)
  - Poster for Rescheduled Quintessence Appearance at Vanderbilt University, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Dr. Mary Daly and Her Case Against Boston College Poster, 2000 (Box 73)
  - Mary Daly: Complete Crone-Ology Article by Janice Raymond, 1979 (Box 73)
  - Daly Diplomas (Box 73)
  - Posters of Feminist Icons, possibly used for teaching (Folder 75)
  - Posters from the Women's Graphic Collective, 1972-1979 (Folder 75)
- SERIES II. Writings, 1973-2004; 30.376 linear feet (38 containers)
  This series contains Daly's records pertaining to her journal articles and books. Materials include manuscripts and drafts, research files, correspondence with publishers, royalty information, and book tour speeches. More correspondence with publishers and all fan mail is located in the correspondence series. Further research files can be found in the personal and correspondence series.
  - Outercourse flyers (Box 16)
  - Wendy Strothman, Beacon, 1989 (Box 16)
  - Beyond God the Father reprint permission, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Beacon royalties, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
  - Beacon permissions, 1994-1999 (Box 16)
  - Daly - publicity, reviews for Quintessence, etc., 1974-2004 (Box 16)
  - Beacon Press catalogues (Box 16)
  - Books ordered by Mary Daly, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Permissions for Wickedary, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Wickedary publicity, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Beacon Press book orders (Mary Daly books), 1987 (Box 16)
  - Beyond God the Father Beacon Press introduction cover, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Wickedary - quality paperback, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Wickedary pages and cover illustrations (Box 16)
  - Wickedary - Women of Power excerpt, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Wickedary regarding label (Box 16)
  - Quintessence - Beacon Press, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
  - Wickedary manuscript - Beacon, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Beacon Press permissions, 1986-1988 (Box 16)
  - Beacon Press publicity, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Indiana University Press, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Permissions requests, 1988-1990 (Box 16)
  - Beacon Press direct mailing promotions (Box 16)
  - Beacon Press receipts, 1985 (Box 16)
  - BGTF - new information, 1984 (Box 16)
  - BGTF publicity (Box 16)
  - Beacon - The Church and the Second Sex, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Beacon permissions - Victoria Baker, 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Harper contract for Pure Lust, 1992 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust publicity, 1984-1986 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust - Beacon publicity expenses, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust - Beacon Press publicity, 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Beacon publicity, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust permission, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Beyond God the Father reviews, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Harper and Row new books, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Royalty records, 1973-1982 (Box 16)
  - Beacon Press, 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Beacon royalties, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust expenses, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust - contractual material, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Beacon Press - Wickedaries - cloth bought by Crone's Harvest, 1989 (Box 16)
  - Church and the Second Sex - Italian, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Beacon royalties, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Church and the Second Sex II royalties, 1975-1985 (Box 16)
  - Off Our Backs, 1984 (Box 16)
  - New York Times Book Reveiw, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust order forms (Box 16)
  - Permision to reprint Guest article, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Send copies of Pure Lust and Gyn/Ecology, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - For Berkshire Women's Newspaper - Pure Lust chapter 4, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust material, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Wickedary publicity, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Frauenoffensive correspondence, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Pope article information (Box 16)
  - Attic Press royalties, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Attic Press Ireland - Wickedary (Box 16)
  - Beyond God the Father Dutch, 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Beyond God the Father Dutch, 1987-1993 (Box 16)
  - Italian contract for Beyond God the Father Riuniti, 1990 (Box 16)
  - New Beyond God the Father publicity, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Swedish publishers ACCA and Matrixx, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Germany and Holland correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - French translation Beyond God the Father, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Beyond God the Father correspondence, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Gyn/Ecology correspondence, 1986 (Box 16)
  - About translation of Outercourse, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Quantitative Leap and other articles - permissions, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Palmer and Dodge Insurance, 1995-1996 (Box 16)
  - Agents and editor, 1995 (Box 16)
  - Harper Collins, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Gyn/Ecology manuscript, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 4 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 10 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 12 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 9 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 11 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 (Box 16)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 (Box 16)
  - Gyn/Ecology fronts piece (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Chapter 4 (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Chapter 5 (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Chapter 6 (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Chapter 7 (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology The Third Passage (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Chapter 8 (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Chapter 9 (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Chapter 10 (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Notes (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Indexes (Box 17)
  - Gyn/Ecology Chapter 3 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Introduction (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 4 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 7 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 9 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 10 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 11 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Introduction (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Preface, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Beyond God the Father (Box 17)
  - Kathy notes (Box 17)
  - Bread and Roses speech (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust Canadian speech (Box 17)
  - Word Lists - Page lists, etc. - 1 (Box 17)
  - Word Lists -Page lists, etc. - 2 (Box 17)
  - Postcard - "Gone with the Wind" (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 1 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 2 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 3 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 4 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript [additional draft] - 1 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript [additional draft] - 2 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript [additional draft] - 3 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript [additional draft] - 4 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript [additional draft] - 5 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 1 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 2 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 3 (Box 17)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 4 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 5 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust manuscript - 6 (Box 18)
  - Paulist Press, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 8 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Introduction (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Cover (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 5 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 6 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 (Box 18)
  - Running as a Secular Religion: A Feminist Analysis by Elaine Koenig, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Orwell notes (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust general notes (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust general notes (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust paper notes (Box 18)
  - Notes (Box 18)
  - Tapes of classes - transcribed, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 3, new ideas (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 4 (Box 18)
  - Criticism (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous materials, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Xeroxes of Chapter 1 draft (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Copies from monographs (Box 18)
  - Newspaper articles, 1980-1983 (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust outline (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust New Preface and Introduction (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Prologue to the First Realm Elementaries (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Prologue to the First Realm (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - General Notes (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Male Names (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Male Lust and other passions (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Female Lust, female passions (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Final Cause (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Memory (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Mirrors (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Male Passions (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Male Cravenness, gall (Box 18)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Male Passions: ill will, reversion, dejection (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Male Passions: lust, conversion, erection, rapality, disintegration (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Male Passions: rancor (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Nukes and Volcanoes (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - S and M (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 1 - Senses (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 - Sublime (Box 19)
  - Pure Lust Chapter 2 - Sublime: Blasphemy (Box 19)